const Data = () => [
  {
    question:
      " What year did the Titanic sink in the Atlantic Ocean on 15 April, on its maiden voyage from Southampton?",
    options: ["1912", "1955", "2000", "2012"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      " If the Earth were made into a black hole, what would be the diameter of its event horizon?",
    options: ["40mm", "20mm", "60mm", "80mm"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you fell down an airless, frictionless hole going all the way through the Earth, how long would it take to fall to the other side? (To the nearest minute.)",
    options: ["55 minutes", "70 minutes", " 42 minutes", "55 minutes"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many hearts does an Octopus Have?",
    options: ["two", "four", "five", "three"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what year was the product WD40 invented by chemist Norm Larsen?",
    options: ["1953", "1999", "2022", "2025"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you took one step each second in seven-league boots, what would your speed be in miles per hour?",
    options: [
      "25,600 miles per hour",
      "75,600 miles per hour",
      "80,000 miles per hour",
      "90,000 miles per hour",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the furthest you can see with the naked eye?",
    options: [
      " 4.5 million light-years",
      " 3.5 million light-years",
      "2.5 million light-years",
      "6.5 million light-years",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "To the nearest thousand, how many hairs are there on a typical human head?",
    options: ["20,000 hairs", "40,000 hairs", "30,000 hairs", "10,000 hairs"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented the gramophone?",
    options: [
      "Emile Berliner",
      "Praveen Rafel",
      "Pedri Suriya",
      "Sabari albert",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: " Who invented man-made fizzy drinks?",
    options: [
      "Prince Batrik",
      "Joseph Priestley",
      "Austin Saravanan",
      "Kavin Eleven",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
];

export default Data();
